There. I'm Scott Menor.
I'm a green party candidate running
to represent Arizona's 14th legislative district
which is basically Gilbert Arizona
in the statehouse
I am running because our democracy is fundamentally broken
money to interests control almost everything.
The duopoly has a stranglehold on our government
and the things that government does have almost nothing to
do with the things that we want and care about.
I wanna change that.
My primary goal
when elected is to pass comprehensive electoral reform which
will make it easier to run for office for citizens
not require so much money, not require huge amounts of signatures
or huge amounts of time and effort to campaign. I want
everybody who feels called to run and to represent people and
who has interests that they want to enact in government.
I want you to have a real chance.
I also want us all to be able to vote for the candidates who best represent us.
I don't want us to feel like we are in a position where we have to strategically vote
for somebody
because the other one is so much worse.
Um
That, that sucks. I'm done with it.
So whether you're a independent, a green, a democrat or a Republican.
I will represent you.
I will talk with you through this. The system is called engage.
And uh basically, I'm hoping that you will share this with your friends, family,
neighbors,
particularly people in Gilbert, but it's open to people anywhere,
uh particularly it's useful for people in the uh
in the actual district though.
Um And then my goal is after that
to get out of office. I, I do not want to be a career politician.
I really uh
it's not my thing. I'm not, I'm not that guy.
Uh
But I, I feel compelled and I feel like somebody needs to do something
and I have some ideas, I think I can do it.
So
thank you for um for paying me attention. Thank you for watching
and I hope we can go on this journey together.
Have a good day.